<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8' ?>
<e107Export version="2.3.1 (git)" timestamp="1617382345" >
	<database>
	<dbTable name="fanfiction_messages">
		<item>
			<field name="message_id">1</field>
			<field name="message_name">welcome</field>
			<field name="message_title"></field>
			<field name="message_text">This is your welcome message. It appears on the index page. Include it in your .tpl files with {welcome}.</field>
		</item>
		<item>
			<field name="message_id">2</field>
			<field name="message_name">copyright</field>
			<field name="message_title"></field>
			<field name="message_text"><![CDATA[ 
<u>Disclaimer:</u>  All publicly recognizable characters, settings, etc. are the property of their respective owners.  The original characters and plot are the property of the author.  No money is being made from this work.  No copyright infringement is intended.<br>
 
]]></field>
		</item>
		<item>
			<field name="message_id">10</field>
			<field name="message_name">tinyMCE</field>
			<field name="message_title"></field>
			<field name="message_text"></field>
		</item>
		<item>
			<field name="message_id">3</field>
			<field name="message_name">help</field>
			<field name="message_title">Help</field>
			<field name="message_text"><![CDATA[<h3>FAQ</h3><p><strong>I forgot my password!&nbsp; What do I do now?</strong></p><p>To recover a lost password, <a href="user.php?action=lostpassword">click here</a> and enter the e-mail address with which you registered.&nbsp; Your password will be sent to you shortly.</p><p><strong>What kinds of stories are allowed?</strong></p><p>See our <a href="submission.php">Submission Rules.</a></p><p><strong>How do I contact the site administrators?</strong></p><p>You can e-mail us via our <a href="contact.php">contact form.</a></p><p><strong>How do I submit stories?</strong></p><p>If you have not already done so, please <a href="user.php?action=newaccount">register for an account</a>. Once you've logged in, click on <a href="user.php">Account Information</a> and choose <a href="stories.php?action=newstory">Add Story</a>.&nbsp; The form presented there will allow you to submit your story.</p><p><strong>What are the ratings used on the site?</strong></p><p>We use the ratings system from <a href="http://www.fictionratings.com/">www.fictionratings.com</a>.</p><p><strong>What are the story classifications?</strong></p><p>Stories are classified by categories, genres, and warnings.</p>]]></field>
		</item>
		<item>
			<field name="message_id">4</field>
			<field name="message_name">nothankyou</field>
			<field name="message_title">Submission Rejection</field>
			<field name="message_text"><![CDATA[Your recent submission of "{storytitle} : {chaptertitle}" to {sitename} did not meet our requirements for submission.  Please review our {rules}.<br /><br />

{adminname}]]></field>
		</item>
		<item>
			<field name="message_id">5</field>
			<field name="message_name">printercopyright</field>
			<field name="message_title"></field>
			<field name="message_text"><![CDATA[<u>Disclaimer:</u> All publicly recognizable characters and settings are the property of their respective owners. The original characters and plot are the property of the author. No money is being made from this work. No copyright infringement is intended.]]></field>
		</item>
		<item>
			<field name="message_id">6</field>
			<field name="message_name">rules</field>
			<field name="message_title">Submission Rules</field>
			<field name="message_text"><![CDATA[[html]<p><strong>Submission Rules</strong></p>
<ol>
<li>All submissions must be accompanied by a complete disclaimer. If a suitable disclaimer is not included, the site administrators reserve the right to add a disclaimer.&nbsp; Repeat offenders may be subject to further action up to and including removal of stories and account.
<div class=&quot;tblborder&quot; style=&quot;width: 400px; margin: 1em auto;&quot;>
<div style=&quot;background: #000; color: #fff; padding: 5px; text-align: center; font-weight: bold;&quot;>Sample Disclaimer</div>
<div class=&quot;tblborder&quot; style=&quot;padding: 5px;&quot;><span style=&quot;text-decoration: underline;&quot;>Disclaimer:</span> All publicly recognizable characters, settings, etc. are the property of their respective owners. The original characters and plot are the property of the author.&nbsp; The author is in no way associated with the owners, creators, or producers of any media franchise.&nbsp; No copyright infringement is intended.</div>
</div>
</li>
<li>Stories must be submitted to the proper category. &nbsp;If there is an appropriate sub-category, <strong>DO NOT</strong> add your story to the main category.&nbsp; The submission form allows you to choose multiple categories for your story, and we worked very hard to add that functionality for you.&nbsp;&nbsp; <u><strong>So please do NOT add your story multiple times!</strong></u></li>
<li>Titles and summaries must be kid friendly.&nbsp; No exceptions.&nbsp;</li>
<li>&quot;Please read&quot;, &quot;Untitled&quot;, etc. are not acceptable titles or summaries.</li>
<li>A number of authors have requested that fans refrain from writing fan fiction based on their work.&nbsp; Therefore submissions will not be accepted based on the works of P.N. Elrod, Raymond Feist, Terry Goodkind, Laurell K. Hamilton, Anne McCaffrey, Robin McKinley, Irene Radford, Anne Rice, and Nora Roberts/J.D. Robb.&nbsp;</li>
<li>Actor/actress stories are not permitted...not even if they&#039;re visiting an alternate reality.</li>
<li>Correct grammar and spelling are expected of all stories submitted to this site.&nbsp; The site administrators are not grammar Nazis.&nbsp; However, the site administrators reserve the right to request corrections in submissions with a multitude of grammar and/or spelling errors.&nbsp; If such a request is ignored, the story will be deleted.</li>
<li>All stories must be rated correctly and have the appropriate warnings.&nbsp; All adult rated stories are expected to have warnings.&nbsp; After all, they wouldn&#039;t have that rating if there wasn&#039;t something to be warned about!&nbsp; The site administrators recognize that there is an audience for these stories, but please respect those who do not wish to read them by labeling them appropriately.&nbsp; <u><strong>Please note: Stories containing adults having sex with minors are strictly forbidden.</strong></u>&nbsp;</li>
<li>Stories with multiple chapters should be archived as such and <span style=&quot;font-weight: bold; text-decoration: underline;&quot;>NEVER</span> as separate stories.&nbsp; Upload the first chapter of your story, then go to <a href=&quot;stories.php?action=viewstories&quot;>Manage Stories</a> in your account to add additional chapters. If you have trouble with this, please contact the site administrator or ask a friend to help you.</li>
<li>As much as possible, spoiler warnings are expected on all stories. For categories with serialized content, such as series of books or television series, spoilers are <strong>mandatory</strong> for the current season and/or most recent part. An appropriate spoiler warning to place in your summary would be: Spoilers for <u>Star Trek II: The Wrath of Khan.</u> <strong>DO NOT</strong> do anything like this: <u>Spoilers for the one where Spock dies.</u></li>
</ol>
<p>Submissions found to be in violation of these rules may be removed and the author&#039;s account suspended at the discretion of the site administrators and/or moderators.&nbsp; The site administrators reserve the right to modify these rules as needed.</p>[/html]]]></field>
		</item>
		<item>
			<field name="message_id">7</field>
			<field name="message_name">thankyou</field>
			<field name="message_title">{sitename} Submission Acceptance</field>
			<field name="message_text">Thanks for your submission.</field>
		</item>
		<item>
			<field name="message_id">8</field>
			<field name="message_name">tos</field>
			<field name="message_title">Terms of Service</field>
			<field name="message_text">This is the Terms of Service for your site.  It will be displayed when a new member registers to the site.</field>
		</item>
		<item>
			<field name="message_id">9</field>
			<field name="message_name">maintenance</field>
			<field name="message_title">Site Maintenance</field>
			<field name="message_text"><![CDATA[<p style="text-align: center;">This site is currently undergoing maintenance.  Please check back soon.  Thank you.</p>]]></field>
		</item>
	</dbTable>
	</database>
</e107Export>